Guide to the Phil Zwickler papers, circa 1979-1993
Zwickler, Phil papers, circa 1979-1993
- Series II. Videos
  - F. Others
    - "WNYC" Tape #2: Gay Rights Hearing, 3-11-86: WNYC/Stock Ftge [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 109
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 10)
    - "WNYC" Tape#4: Gay Rights Hearing, 3-11-86: WNYC/Stock Ftge [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 110
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 10)
    - "WNYC" Tape #5: Gay Rights Hearing, 3-11-86: WNYC/Stock Ftge [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 111
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 10)
    - "WNYC" Tape #6: Gay Rights Hearing, 3-11-86: WNYC/Stock Ftge [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 112
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 10)
    - "WNYC" Tape #7: Gay Rights Hearing, 3-11-86: WNYC/Stock Ftge [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 113
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 10)
    - "WNYC" Wrap-Up: Gay Rights Hearing, 3-11-86: WNYC/Stock Ftge [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 114
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 10)
    - "WNYC" Gay Rights Bill Council Vote + Vote for the Record [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 115
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
    - "WNYC" Council Vote, 1-5-87 [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 116
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
    - "WNYC" Council Vote [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 117
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
    - "WNYC" Council Vote [WNYC has rights!!] [ RESTRICTED], 118
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
    - Sodomy Protest [12 min.], 119
      - Original, V-177; 3/4" (Box 11)
      - Use copy, V-172; VHS (Box 14)
    - A.D.A.P.T. [10 min.], 120
      - Original, VHS (Box 12)
    - Stock Footage Brooklyn Streets 1982 [ETG Masters] Central Park Live, Odd bits, 121
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
    - "Selects": Dignity 3-7-87, 122
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
    - "No Timid Reply" - excerpt of a work in progress, 1986, 123
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
    - Tape 1: Andy Humm speech 7/4/86, Cam Orig., 124
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
      - Use copy, V-173; VHS (Box 14)
    - "Positive" and "Silence = Death", 160; Features Phil Zwickler; VHS (Box 20)
  - Master Edit
    - "A Christmas Wish" (with Bayard Rustin), 11/26/89, 1081; Sections of this tape were preserved on DVC tape, item #162; This section may also be found on-line at http://rmc.library.cornell.edu/HSC/zwickler/nav.htm; 125
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 11)
      - SP Betacam (Box 20)
      - Use Copy (Box 15)
    - "No Timid Reply": NYC Gay Community responds to U. S. Supreme Court Anti-Sodomy ruling - 1986, 126
      - Original, V-176; 3/4" (Box 9)
      - Use copy, V-171; VHS (Box 14)
    - "Our Own Parade" PEW/GCN - Edit Master, 7/6/86 - PZ 1986 - 12 min., 127
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
    - Phil Zwickler Memorial Service (1 of 3), 6/1/91, RSM# 1077A; 128
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
      - Use Copy, VHS (Box 17)
    - Phil Zwickler Memorial Service (2 of 3), 6/1/91, RSM# 1077B; 129
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
      - Use Copy, VHS (Box 17)
    - Phil Zwickler Memorial Service (3 of 3), 6/1/91, RSM# 1077C; 130
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
      - Use Copy, VHS (Box 17)
    - PZ Memorial 6/1/91 #1, 131
      - Beta cam (Box 12)
    - PZ Memorial 6/1/91 #2, 132
      - Beta cam (Box 12)
    - PZ Memorial 6/1/91 #3, 133
      - Beta cam (Box 12)
  - Demo Tapes
    - 1. NY Post Demonstration 12/1/85, 2. AIDS Memorial Service 12/23/85, 3. Film Festival Demonstration 1/9/86, 134
      - Original, 3/4"; USE COPY (VHS) IN BOX 14 (Box 11)
      - Use copy, VHS (Box 14)
  - Others
    - AIDS Memorial Service: Cathedral of St. John's, 12/23/85, James Taylor, Bishop Moore, 135
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - New York Gay Film Festival Opening Night Demonstration 1/9/86 master edit, 136
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
    - Misc. Demo Film Fest NY Gay; Dub D, 137
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
    - 18 minute Best of, 8:00, August 11, 1986 Demonstration: Master Edit, 138
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Fran, 139
      - Beta cam (Box 12)
    - Fran, 140
      - Beta cam (Box 12)
    - "Shox Lumania," Charles Smith - Manager, 141
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 9)
    - Central Park History #1, 142
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Central Park History #2, 143
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Central Park Stills, Autumn 1981, 144
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Central Park Stills, Autumn 1981, 145
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: 20 M R 10/6 Camera 2 Original, 146
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Tape 2 7/4/86 Camera Original, 147
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Tape #1: Protest Oct. 6, 1986, 148
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Gays rights bill #2, 149
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Lesb + Gay March on B'way Protest: Cam Orig, July 4, 1986, Tape 4, 150
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Freedom Voyage #2 (Berger 3), 151
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Lesb + Gay March on B'way: Cam Orig, #3, 7/4/86, 152
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Protest #1: Coalition Lesbian + Gay Protest / Great Car Race #2, 153
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Coalition Lesbian + Gay Rights Protest, 154
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Coalition Lesbian + Gay Protest, 8/11 Tape 1, 155
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Great Car Race #2; Great American Car Race #1; Freedom Voyage #1; Berger #4, 156
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - Coalition Gay and Lesbian Protest Gay Rights Bill - Sodomy Issue: Protest #2, Aug. 11, Comm., 157
      - Original, 3/4" (Box 13)
    - "Rights and Reactions": Final Version (56 min.), October 28, 1987; RSM#; 158
      - Use Copy, VHS (Box 17)
    - "Fear of Disclosure": Phil Zwickler and David Wojnarowicz, 1989; RSM# 1115; 159
      - Use Copy, VHS, also a DVD copy (DVD-1174) (Box 17)
    - Needle Nightmare, 1991; RSM# 1140; 161
      - Use Copy, VHS (Box 14)
    - Segments of Items 99, 100, 125, 162; DVC tape (Box 14)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis Network interview of Phil Zwickler; Bayard Rustin interview; Needle Nightmare film; Fear of Disclosure film, 164; DVD (Box 14)
    - Interview of Phil at his Newsline office, 165; DVD (Box 14)
      A portion of this interview is available at www.pzfoundation.org
    - Speeches and newspaper headlines that occurred during the time of the passage of the Gay Rights bill, 166; DVD (Box 14)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The First 10 Years, GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis 1990-1991 Annual Report)
1990-1991
One
1954: 2:8 (Oct.)
Christopher Street
1981: 2:11, Issue 59
The Advocate
1987: Issue 485 (Nov. 10)
"Image", San Francisco Examiner ("Gay in America", Examiner special report)
1989: (June 4)
Ringling Bros. and Barnum and Bailey Circus (Brochure- Gay Men's Health Crisis Benefit to Fight AIDS)
1983: (April 30)
Good Intentions: How Big Business and the Medical Establishment Are Corrupting the Fight Against AIDS, Alzheimer's, Cancer and More by Bruce Nussbaum
1990
You Can Do Something About AIDS, Sasha Alyson, ed. (publication of the Stop AIDS Project, Inc.)
1988
PWA Coalition Newsline
1990: Issue 51 (Jan.); Issue 53 (March); Issue 54 (April); Issue 55 (May); Issue 56 (June); Issue 57 (July/Aug.); Issue 58 (Sept.); Issue 59 (Oct.); Issue 60 (Nov.); Issue 61 (Dec.)
PWA Coalition Newsline
1991: Issue 62 (Jan./Feb.); Issue 63 (March); Issue 64 (April); Issue 65 (May); Issue 66 (June); Issue 67 (July); Issue 68 (Aug.); Issue 69 (Sept.); Issue 70 (Oct.); Issue 72 (Dec.)
PWA Coalition Newsline
1992: Issue 74 (March); Issue 75 (April); Issue 76 (May); Issue77 (June); Issue 78 (July); Issue 81 (Oct.)1993: Issue 86 (April)